http://www.skymall.com/pages/privacy-policy

Home Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Statement reflects our commitment to fair information practices. Individuals who interact with C&A Marketing, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, the “Company”) are entitled to understand how personal information about them will be collected, used and disclosed. Whenever possible, we explain how personal information can be corrected, updated or deleted. We keep personal information secure.
This Privacy Statement describes what type of information we collect, use, process, share, disclose, store, transfer and dispose of, including personal information (i.e., information that personally identifies you, such as your name, email address or billing information, or other data that can be reasonably used to infer this information, whether sensitive or not) through this website (“Site”). This Privacy Statement also applies to other websites where the Company’s products and/or services are likewise made available to the public online, provided that the Company has control over the personal information collected or processed through such channels.
Your use of this Site indicates that you have read, accepted and agreed to this Privacy Statement and any other applicable document referred to herein. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SITE.
Collection and Use
Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.  Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall. For more information, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service (https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or Shopify’s Privacy Statement (https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).
The Company collects and processes information about you through our Site in a variety of ways. This information is used to allow us to understand how visitors like you navigate our Site, and to provide advertising that may be relevant to your interests.
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.
Should you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent with respect to continued collection, use or disclosure of your information at any time by contacting us at the following:
SkyMall 114 Tived Lane East
Edison New Jersey US 08837
customerservice@SkyMall.com
Examples of collected information are outlined below:
Account Information
If you set up and Account or order products from our Site, we may request that you provide your name, email address, billing and shipping address, credit card information, telephone number, and any other information necessary to complete the transaction.
Please note though that we do not collect or store your full credit card information. Our credit card processing service providers will collect and store full payment card information from you when an order is placed, and until the order is shipped. If you create an Account your payment information may be stored for future use whenever you need it.
If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.
Mailing List Information
If you sign up for our newsletter, we may request that you provide your name, email address, and any other information necessary to include you in our mailing list.
We may use one or more service providers to administer these messages, but we do not share your email address with spammers or any other third parties without your permission. You can opt out of receiving our marketing and promotional emails about our brands and products. To stop receiving our marketing and promotional emails, follow the instructions in any marketing email you get from us.
Usage Data
We may record the IP address you use and analyze data collected through cookies and other tracking technology to collect information about your browsing behavior when you visit our Site. Please refer to our Ad and Cookie Policy for more information.
Third-Party Sites and Features
Our Site may contain links to other websites operated by third parties and may include social media features that the Company does not control. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the same.
Minors
By using this Site, you represent that you have attained the age of majority in your jurisdiction and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this Site. Our Site does not knowingly collect or store any personal information about children under the age of 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or guardian and you think your child under 13 has given us information, please contact us at customerservice@SkyMall.com .
Data Sharing
We do not share your personal information for any commercial or marketing purpose. We also have strict policies and technical barriers in place to prevent unauthorized employee access to your data.
Please note though that we may have vendors, service providers, and technicians who help with some of our processing and storage of information, including helping to answer your questions. In general, these third-party providers us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us. They may also assist with monitoring our servers for technical problems.
These technicians can access certain information about you in line with this work but these technicians are not allowed to use this data for unauthorized purposes.
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.  For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers. Once you leave our Site or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Statement or our Site’s Terms of Service. Furthermore, certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either of us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
In the event that the Company, or all or part of its assets is sold or transferred to a third party, your personal information may be among the items sold or transferred as well. If such is indeed the case, we will request the purchaser to secure and treat your data in accordance with the Privacy Policy in place at the time of its collection.
We may also provide information to a third party if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so for legal reasons, such as, disclosures pursuant to legal processes, U.S. state and federal laws, or foreign laws.
We may also share non-personal information (e.g., de-identified or aggregate data) publicly and with our partners and, in some cases, to other users to help us generally improve our products and services. Please note though that we employ methods to keep this data from being associated with you and require our partners to do the same.
Your personal information may be collected, processed and stored by the Company or its service providers in the United States and other countries outside the European Union where our servers reside. As a result, your personal information may be subject to legal requirements, including transborder transfer of data regulations or other lawful requirements to disclose personal information to government authorities. You also agree to comply with all applicable export and import laws and regulations.
Security
The security and integrity of your personal information is of paramount concern to us and we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
For this reason, we use commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technological methods to collect, process, transmit and store your data securely. If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.
However, by using our Site, you understand that the Company cannot guarantee unauthorized access at all times as no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure. In the event this occurs, we will take reasonable steps to investigate, notify those affected whenever appropriate, and take other steps in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations. We follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards to ensure your data is protected.
International Visitors and Data Transfers
The Site is subject to U.S. laws, which may not provide the same level of protection as those in your country. If you live outside the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States or our offices in other countries.  If you are accessing the site from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, you may be engaging in transborder transfer of data. By providing your personal data in our Site, you consent to that transfer.
Changes and Concerns
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will provide notice of any changes on the website or by informing you when appropriate.
If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, have a dispute with us about our adherence to applicable law, or have any concern regarding your personal information, please contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at:
SkyMall 114 Tived Lane East
Edison New Jersey US 08837
customerservice@SkyMall.com
Last Updated: [1 September 2017]
Free Shippingon all orders over $50
Guaranteedunbeatable prices
Easy Returns30 days - hassle free
114 Tived Lane E
Edison, NJ 088371-800-SKYMALLcustomerservice@skymall.comSubscribe To Our Mailing List
Rewards ProgramBuy eGift CardsAffiliate ProgramSubmit Your Product
Help & Info
ReturnsFAQShipping & DeliveryPayment PoliciesTerms of ServicePrivacy StatementAd & Cookie PolicyIntellectual Property Guidelines
Copyright © 2017, SkyMall Holdings LLC. All Rights Reserved.
Cancer and Reproductive Harm - www.P65Warnings.ca.gov
0
x
